The End Ah, crap!
The food is bad.
Bepo! Bepo!
Bepo!
Co-bro's dead!
Not just that he was murdered I mean I
never liked the guy but I didn't want
him to get whacked by Eldridge Stevens
this is sick I was not supposed to say
I figured the world
government had something
seedy going on but not
whatever the hell that was!
Who is that guy?
I'm screwed! I'm dead!
No king cobra.
And no king Wapol today either.
We just received word.
That their Highness wish for you
to begin the meeting without them.
Seems that big speech wore king cobra out.
Let him have a nap.
He must be satisfied.
Now that the matter of
the warlords is closed.
Well then.
Let's look at the rest of the agenda.?
The Four Nation Alliance in the North
Blue is calling for independence.
Time to mumble.
Let's shake away the sorrow.
Shirahoshi, the council
will be over soon enough.
Let's wait at the port where
those cretins won't come.
All right.
What's wrong?
Before we leave, I wanted to say
a few words to Princess Vivi.
I wonder where she ran off to.
Do you think you'll get away with this?
You're insane!
Untie me now!
Who are you working for?
I'm going to tell the
world what you've done.
Just you wait and see!
You know, you're too
honest for your own good.
We can't set you free after hearing that.
I like your fire, though.
Hate to break it to you, princess.
But no one is coming for you,
no matter how much you whine.
You'll be reported missing.
Then live out the rest of
your days as someone's pet.
Is Shirahoshi all right? What?
You're really asking about
someone else right now?
It sounds like there was
another incident with her.
But long story short, she's just fine.
Thank goodness.
Apparently, a couple of guys beat up
the Celestial Dragon who was after her.
We fear nothing because we
work for Stronghold Luffy!
They made sure everyone
knew what they were about.
Now it seems the whole
plaza's in an uproar.
And then, to make matters worse,
Fujitora started helping the
revolutionaries free the slaves.
Ryokugyu didn't take too
kindly to that, of course.
And that's the story.
It's a damn joke calling
this shit show a reverie.
I have to escape.
I'm not going to be kept as some pet.
Think, Vivi.
Someone help me!
I didn't see anything, I swear!
Wubble?
Get off my wad!
I didn't do nothing, do you hear me?
Leave me alone!
Just out of the world!
Anyone want to guess what that was about?
Was that King Waffle?
Wait a second!
Where the hell is Vivi?!
You there!
Yes, Queen Kinderella!
Have you seen my husband?
No, your majesty, not today.
King Muffle!
Darling, I've been
looking all over for you!
Where did you run off to?
Why is there a woman in your mouth?
How far are you planning to run like this?
As far as I came, to the end of
the world where no one was...
Oh, they…
sounds good to me.
Take me to…
F .A .R .L .O .B .A .N.
But it's one thing to shine.
I'm going to give you
a message to the body.
Beach Beach No Limit.
Here is one piece.
All of us, the people who
are living in the world.
That's the dream is not yet to go away.
I can't sleep, I can't sleep.
I can't sleep.
I'm still trying to conquer the world.
I'm not going to conquer the world.
There's no way to conquer the world.
I'm still trying to
conquer the world.
A pact is made to make the world.
The murder of King
Cobra was kept a secret.
So most of the monarchs at the reverie.
Prepared to leave without a
hint that anything was wrong.
I demand to see King Cobra.
We were ordered not to allow anyone in.
Leave at once. I told you.
Our king is in poor health.
Let me see him now.
Get back.
King Cobra.
Excuse me.
Has anyone seen Princess Vivi?
From the kingdom of Alabasta?
She looks like this.
Heaven if you've seen her.
Where did you go, Princess Vivi?
Please be safe.
Let's hurry up! Careful!
Those belong to one of the royal families.
Don't let them get damaged.
Right!
King T IV is on board and waiting!
Hurry and bring his belongings! Yes, sir!
Gotta say this is going
better than I expected
we should be safe for the time being but
what's the next step tell the world what
happened the whole story
I don't deserve any of
this all I did was paint through a hole in
the wall and now they
want to kill me for the
last time keep your
voice down wait a sec I
just realized I gotta
take it out of this mess
he won't let me down when I gotta
scoop like this you have a transponder
snail what a pleasant surprise did you
have a nice time at the reverie let's
not talk about that right now sounds
like something juicy happened spill
it no can do buddy they'll ice me for
sure I'll have to tell you in person
but if you hide me I'll give you the
scope of a lifetime I swear fair enough
for starters where are you right now
hey what do I tell them whose ship
are we on the eggies kingdoms interesting
we'll swap in and tell them we're
researching a story then sneak on my ship
and don't be seen I owe you one. So, look.
This is big news.
Sounds like things got unhinged, royally
unhinged, if a king's life is at stake.
Now this is what I live for!
Anyway, what did you see? Tell me.
You don't want to know.
And I mean you specifically
don't want to know, okay?
So go back to your own
kingdom and stop bugging me!
I can't.
It was CP0 who captured me.
Even if I make it back home, he'll just
take me into custody again by force.
So let me use your
transponder, snail. But why?
Because my father needs to know I'm safe.
He worries about me.
Oh, hell no!
Absolutely not!
Don't even try!
Why not?
And what does it matter to you?
Oh, I'm so hungry.
I just have to hold out
until I get to La Lucia.
I'm counting on you, Zeff.
You must live on.
With the reverie coming to a close,
the monarchs departed for their homes,
unaware of what happened behind the scenes
and of who was stowing
away on their ships.
However, even if the truth was
obscured by the government,
the news of King Cobra's
murder spread like wildfire?
as did tidings of Princess
Vivi's disappearance.
I suppose it was only a matter of time
before Sabo crossed our paths like this.
His life has been intertwined
with the D at nearly every turn.
Egghead should be our priority right now.
It's time to put the matter to rest.
Yes, Great Emu?
I wish to use Vegapunk's invention.
Let us see how well the
Mother Flame performs.
We're still not certain
if it can deliver or not.
Now would be as good a
time as any to find out.
Let's postpone our plans for Egghead.
They may change based on
the results of this test.
We'll aim for a forested area.
Testing it at sea won't do.
The kingdom of Lulusia men.
Quite a number of people live there.
It matters not.
As you wish, of course.
The world should be just as
its creators will it after all.
But may I ask, why Lulusia?
It's close.
Indeed.
understood we'll make preparations
now it won't be long it's just as
well there have been signs of revolt
in the lucille this will set an
example for the rest of the world if
it works we'll have a very powerful
weapon at our disposal and our
long-fought battle will come to an end
i have one more request what
is it i desire vv as you wish
I have a report, Fleet Admiral.
There are revolts in the Dadan
Kingdom and the Aegis Kingdom.
Our course is clear.
Time to crush every last one of them.
Load the ammo! Hurry!
Deploy the Seraphim!
Order a full assault!
Alert from empty bluffs.
Crocodiles been sighted.
Thanks to the abolition of
the Seven Warlords system?
And the recent increase in uprisings?
The Navy was busier than
ever before. However,
this was also the start of a different
approach and an aggressive new campaign.
As soon as we arrived at La Lucia, King
Seki and Princess Comane were captured.
The citizens were lying
in wait with an ambush.
They'd had enough.
Let me out of this cage.
NOOOOOO!
They found me and welcomed
me as a hero. I was lucky.
Well, I wouldn't call it luck.
After all you've done, it's no
surprise that you give people hope.
When I saw the newspaper, I
realized it was more than that.
They were celebrating because they
thought I'd assassinated King Cobra.
What could I say to them when
they were all cheering for me?
I wanted to tell them
the truth, of course.
And yet I held my tongue, because
I felt their hunger for revolution.
We can thank Betty for that.
When they met her, plenty of them
wanted to join the Revolutionary Army.
Those are the ones I
brought here, on the ship.
At the time, I wasn't able to get my
hands on an encrypted transponder snail,
which is why I didn't contact you.
Not till we set sail, at least.
That's when I sent you a relay
message, which I'm sure seemed odd.
Dragon, it's true that King Cobra is dead.
But I didn't kill him.
Since it wasn't encrypted,
the government likely intercepted the
call and thought I was at Lulusia.
But in reality, I was already
out at sea with the Enlistees.
And Lulusia was destroyed when
you were on the call with us.
My, must have been traumatic
for those on board. Yeah.
Everyone on the ship went into a panic.
So many of them had just
left their families behind.
And then right before their eyes,
everything was wiped out in a flash.
I'm sure they were devastated.
Can you try to explain what you saw?
A massive shadow covered the sky.
It came out of nowhere.
And then, only a moment later.
What do you mean, a shadow?
I couldn't make it out, because
it was flying above the clouds.
But it was something
dark, something unnatural.
The person you saw you said their
name was emu is that correct?
Yeah well this might sound rather Bizarre
but that name has history 800 years ago
there was a ruler among the first 20 Saint
emu of the neurona dynasty look at this
You've heard the story
there is an ability that
can make someone immortal
they say And it seems
we found that someone
they don't know death and
they're the one calling
the shots at The top of the
world you think that's
the person i saw the
same emu it could be a
coincidence but That seems
unlikely the five elders
who stand above even the
celestial dragons humble
themselves Before emu who
else could claim an authority
like that commanding
the Self-proclaimed
descendants of gods one
more thing this one is
terrifying too That shadow
you saw in the sky is
likely a secret government
weapon but who could Create
something so powerful
a genius that's who what
if it was vegapunk that
Doesn't make sense perhaps
he could but vegapunk
would never design a weapon
to Commit mass murder
i know but in that case
it must be an ancient
weapon if emu is an ancient
human Then that's hardly
a big leap well we do
know that the ancient
weapons exist robin confirmed
As much and yet if the
government's had one for
so long then why haven't
they tried to use it
before And why are they
using it now
we
return to
the present day a celestial
dragon has Been executed
in the rejoin however
this shocking event will
never be reported to
The world good riddance
that traitor sided against
his own people now those
Filthy creatures are
pushing their luck he got
what he deserved now we
can't even Properly and
it's all his fault the
judge was a man famous for
his exploits on an island
known as God valley he
is the supreme commander
of the holy knights his
name saint figalan garling
And the man he executed was the defender
of the fishmen saint don quixote miozgard
Stand up, a subhuman scum,
and you sink even lower.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.